

## **PROFILE**

An extremely motivated and focused accountant with more than 10 years' experience in financial reporting and accountancy. A broad and comprehensive knowledge of QuickBooks software and financial procedures and a keen eye for detail leads to fluid and transparent bookkeeping and in turn client satisfaction.

## CONTACT

### Phone:

+92-322-2480210

#### **Email:**

sajid\_shehzad@hotmail.com

# **HOBBIES**

Reading Books Playing Cricket

## **PERSONAL DETAILS**

**Father Name:** Abdul Rahim **D.O.B** : 04<sup>th</sup> October 1985

Marital Status: Married
Nationality: Pakistani
Religion: Islam

## Address:

Flat # 12-M, Zehra Arcade, Bukshan Village, Gizri, Karachi. Pakistan

# Sajid Shehzad

# Senior Finance Executive

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelors in Commerce (B.com) - Karachi University Intermediate - Govt. Urdu Arts/Commerce College Matriculation - Brooklyn Secondary School

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## BY Ventures LLC - Senior Finance Executive

01-12-2016 - Present

Reporting – Taxation – A/c Receivables – Payables – Invoicing – Payroll – Audit and perform other accounting tasks timely.

# KN Terry Tex - Senior Accountant

01-08-2015 - 30-11-2016

Tax E filling – Import/Export Payments – Expenses – Bank Reconciliation – A/c Receivable and A/c Payable.

## King Chemicals Corporation - Account Executive

01-12-2010 - 31-07-2015

Customer Service – Aging – Invoicing – Managing Receipts & Payments – Administration Tasks – HR Record keeping – Inventory Audit – Store Supervising – Cash Handling and perform other timely assigned tasks.

# Pervaiz Brothers - Accounts Assistant

01-02-2006 - 30-11-2010

Manual Cash Book – Sale/Purchase Report – Posting – Bank Reconciliations – Petty Cash – Admin /HR Tasks.

## **SKILLS**

QuickBooks Accounting Software
Tally Accounting Software
Dotnet Accounting Software
Foxpro Accounting Software
Outlook
Spredsheets
Ms Office
Database Management
Typing

AutoCAD Program
Air Ticketing Program